Speaker: And just as you mentioned at the beginning of the show, you know, it’s
– we all have stories, things, you know, your mum, the smell of cooking, it makes us feel safe and secure.
And it might be a pair of shoes that your dad wore and the smell of the leather,
or it might be the smell of your newborn child.
I can remember the smell of my son when he was born.
I’ve never been able to recreate it, but it’s, it’s the smell of new life for me.
So, I think smell is a really powerful, memory evoking – it’s the nearest thing,
sits by the brain near the memory,
which is why my dyslexia and my being able to create fragrance is
what life took away with one hand, it gave me back with another because they sit side by side.